Papa.
Whoa!
Did she just smack her own alley?
So was it you?
The one who burned Okoboday Town?
Hey! Huh?
You're dead!
I'm gonna squash you ever,
ever so flat, Big Mom!
Nobody hurts my Papa! Uh-oh! Wait!
Maybe we can have Big
Mom beat up Ulti, too!
You know, I thought Big Mom was a
demon, but maybe she's really a goddess.
Hey!
Boleyn, listen!
That lady is seriously bad!
She's the one who did the
awful thing that made you sad!
Whatever that is...
Oh, shut up!
You think I'm dumb?
You're still my enemy!
When I'm done with
Trampasaurus, you're next!
Hurrah!
Go, Ulti! You got this!
Let's avenge Papa together! Oh, shut up!
You think I'm dumb?
When I'm done with that hag, you're next!
Komachiyo, let's book it!
Go and don't look back!
Huh? Hey!
Stay there!
I still need to smash you!
Ulti!
Spider!
Komachiyo!
I'm coming, buddy!
I'm ever, ever so sick of
chasing you little dirtbags.
And that goes for your big weird dog, too.
I hope that headbutt broke some bones.
A whole bunch of them.
Stay away!
Look at the poor little
puppy, all beat up.
That's what you get for being naughty!
Now, play dead!
Damn it!
Stop it, you big man!
Tama!
He's my best friend!
He died, you had his idea!
Shut up, rat!
Tama!
Otama!
Are you okay?
Come on, let's go!
Carry her and run, Nami!
We're all gonna die! Hey!
Bitch!
Huh?
How dare you lay a hand
on my little friend! Ugh!
on my little brother!
You filthy lizard!
How could you do that to a mother?!
Nami, stop it!
We gotta go!
I'm sorry!
Not this time!
I can't!
Not when she hit a child?
This is personal!
I'll kick her ass myself!
I don't know.
Onore-ro-jitsu-wo-e-gai-desu-te
Aye, that's Black-Legged Surge!
He's got a bounty of 330 million berries!
How tough can he be?
Hey, who's that dude he's carrying?
It's gotta be the Pirate Hunter Sorrel!
They're crewmates! What?
That's Big Money carrying bigger money!
Hey, watch what you say!
Sorry big money is carrying
slightly less big money.
That's not the issue.
Oh Am I too noisy?
So sorry.
Hey!
Oh!
Well, well captain kid captain kid?
Wait, sorry, but you're not getting
through glad you guys showed up.
I need some more scrap
You, on the other hand, I don't need you!
Suck on this!
You're done!
Big Mom, where are you?
Good luck, I guess. Damn it.
That must have swapped us
with something in the air.
Huh?
Blackleg?
Is that Traffy and Mosshead?
Don't let us fall!
I thought you were on the roof.
Why are you here?
Where the heck am I?
And where did Mama go?
I'm coming, Mama, I promise!
Zeus!
What are you doing?
Where's Nami?
I thought you were working for her now.
Hey, come back here! Leave him be.
Why the hell are you still sitting on me?
This space is reserved for ladies only!
I'm glad we ended up here.
We could use the help.
Oh, yeah, sure.
Just pop out of nowhere
and give me orders.
Just take care of him.
He's injured.
What happened to him?
Hey, wait!
Can't you at least explain
the situation first?
He's in real bad shape.
Probably broke 20 or 30 bones.
Splint up his body, put him on his back.
Make sure he's conscious and breathing.
I'm worried about the battle,
not this idiot's health!
You're the doctor!
Why the hell don't you take care of him?
I would, but I need to shut down Big Mom.
You can do first aid at least.
What am I supposed to do?
Just don't let him die!
Hey!
Don't walk away from me!
I told you I'm not the doctor here!
You don't know how to
apply bandage, do you?
I've trussed a ham before,
it's basically the same thing.
So I'm a ham to you.
No way you taste that good. Never mind.
Anyway.
So, uh, who managed to hurt you this bad?
Kaido and Big Mom together.
No wonder.
Well, at least you found the roof.
I take it Luffy's in
better shape than you.
It's been rough, but I think
he figured something out.
He's gonna win this.
You don't have to tell me that.
What a mess!
I'd stuff your ass in a
closet if I had it my way!
Sir Sangoro!
Uh, Kappa.
Glad to see you guys are all right.
Uh, hey, Nami.
I get that you're angry, but
we gotta run away, quick!
She won't be out for long!
You saw how many times her
brother came back to get us!
Also, Big Mom is right there!
No matter how you look
at it, we can't win!
Even if we run, Ulti won't stop chasing
us until we take her out for good!
But more than that, I'm not letting
her go after what she did to Otama.
Come on, Otama.
Hang in there.
Otama, tell me you're okay.
I know you're not dead.
Get up already.
Just can't wait for me to bust your
head open like a big ripe melon.
Oh, you see that, boys?
She's got a baton!
This cheerleader thinks she can
take out Lady Ulti on her own!
Tornado!
Tickle!
That was a nice surprise
attack, but it's not enough!
You done yet?
Time to die.
Oh you want some too?
Don't worry weird little man.
Once I'm done with her you are next.
I've hated your guts from
the first moment we met.
Not only do you scurry away
like a rat every chance you get,
You also said your crappy little captain
was gonna be king of the pirates,
but no big deal, right?
It'll all be worth it once I
finally smash your skull in!
Palti!
Oh, Nami, please don't die.
Yes, Mama! Yes, Mama!
Let's go!
Come on!
Mesa-chanal!
She took out Lady Ulti in one shot.
And she took out her brother
just a second ago, too.
Whose side is she supposed to be on?
Nami, can you stand?
That was crazy, but she's finished.
Let's run away. Right.
Call Mathieu.
We can't save him now. I'm sorry.
We'll come back later.
I promise.
Huh? Zeus?
If he's there, who's that other cloud?
Wow!
We really hit it off, didn't we, Hera?
I could never pull off such an awesome
combo attack with stupid old Zeus.
We made a pretty amazing team,
too, wouldn't you say, Hera?
You sad little simpletons are
getting ahead of yourselves.
All I did was follow Mama's lead.
Look at you teasing me. Aww.
I'm so glad I asked Mama
to make me a girlfriend.
And now here you are in the cloudy flesh.
Your girlfriend?
No, thank you. What?
That's okay.
I like my ladies a little fiery.
And either way, it's nice
to have a girl in the group.
Prometheus?
I agree.
So let's work together to
be Mama's best helpers ever.
Napoleon?
Glad I threw Zeus out with the trash.
Seems you three will
make a much better team.
This is messed up.
Who is that girl? Indeed.
Zeus set a good example of what not to do.
She's mean.
Why is she taking my place?
Does this mean I'm gonna
be all alone from now on?
It's not me!
You finally turned up. Hey, Mama.
I'm sorry I kept you waiting.
Looks like we have a new member, huh?
Well, four's better
than three, I say. Four?
I'm afraid you're mistaken.
You've been replaced.
We don't need you.
Remarkable.
Where are you headed?
We'll gladly accompany you.
For what it's worth, my
sword is at your service.
What do you mean, where am I headed?
I'm looking for Momonosuke.
I thought you were too.
Kin'emon is going to aid him.
He should be fine.
If you want to help, go
to the performance floor.
Why would we go there?
Don't make a request
and fall asleep, dammit!
I see no reason not to go.
Yes, let's hurry.
Any life we can save is a victory.
Thunder!
Wild War!
Yeah!
You're having fun playing
with your new toy, aren't you?
And I'm sure it's even more fun to try
it out on someone stronger than you.
I tore down one wall after another,
laying waste to everyone
who was stronger than me.
Until the world had no
choice but to call me the
strongest But what do I
see from these heights?
A barren landscape, filled with weak
wings There's nowhere left to climb!
You wouldn't understand.
You can smile, because you still
have someone worth fighting!
But you can't win, you're
just indulging in a lie.
This country will bend to my will.
A Kozuki clan will be destroyed.
Water will become new Onigashima,
and I'll be bored again.
Alone with my strength.
The Kozuki clan's not going anywhere!
The land of Wano will be free!
And then you'll see!
What the hell I'm gonna
be king of the pirates
mama could have been killed
while you were snoozing?
On the job but they
captured me stop acting like
that was the first time
you screwed something up!
The good news is it will
be the last time mama Ah!
Hera, how about you eat Zeus for me? What?
By consuming his soul,
you'll become even stronger.
How could you say that, Mama?
I'll die!
I'm sure he'll be delectable.
Let's see!
What are all those
flavors for me, O 'Kara?
Stop her mama!
She keeps this up all the time!
Ah, ma-ma-ma! Ha-ha!
I'm so sorry!
I didn't mean to do a bad job!
If you don't want me, then
I promise I'll go away!
Stop swearing!
You're on the fear of my left hand!
I'll never show I think to
you guys again, I swear it!
So please, don't do this to me!
I don't wanna die!
I gave you a piece of my
soul and you're running off?
Why should I have mercy on a filthy thief?
If you're really sorry, you'll let
her eat you and give your power back.
Anything but that, please.
It's what you deserve.
Right, Otama?
Oh, crap.
What the?
Let's move you out of the
way while I kill them.
I'll keep you safe. Otama!
You're awake.
You had me so worried.
Stay there and don't move, sweetie.
Oh, Nami, there's a hot shake!
Ignore those two.
They're from a very naughty
pirate crew called the Straw Hats.
Not to worry, though.
I'm gonna kill them!
Get back here!
Don't hurt them, Elaine!
They're my friends!
They're not bad guys!
They came here to take the country!
Mama, Mama!
Someone help!
Nami!
Huh?
I'm so sorry!
I shouldn't have tried
to kill you, I know!
I am really sorry, Nami!
I shouldn't have known you at all!
You pathetic little coward!
I am so over you!
I failed you!
I couldn't...
I know to mama!
Dorry!
I was afraid of what she might do,
so I betrayed you even though
you were so nice to me!
I'm just a useless
coward, but I'm so sorry!
It's too late now!
I told you we're done,
didn't I? Come on! I know!
And now, Mama and everybody
else hates me too!
I don't have anyone else to go!
I do!
I'll die just like I deserve to!
But I don't want to die
with everyone hating me!
I want you to see this!
That's enough!
But I want to be brave at
least once, before I die!
Tama!
Usahachi!
Let's hurry!
You don't have to forgive me, but
I need to make this up to you!
Then I can die!
Nami!
Run away!
It's not must throw up
from my life for you!
Zeus, wait!
Zeus?
That's all I've got. Goodbye.
Oh, no.
Is that a soul coming out?
Nice job!
Finish him off!
You little idiot!
I'll give you a snack out of pity!
Eat them and run, okay, dude?
Hurry!
She really did take his soul!
He's not even going
for his favorite snack!
Eat them! Come on!
Wake up!
Here I go!
It's dinnertime for moi!
Come on!
Fight it!
Such power!
Oh my!
She ate him!
Uzuhachi! Onami! Let's hurry!
Otama!
There's no time!
Let's go!
Utama, why are you running away?
I see.
You're leaving me, huh?
Fine, then.
Seems you want to be my enemy.
Don't look back!
Once you cross me, there's
only one way it can end.
Mama's gonna kill you!
It's you!
Are you done!
Mama!
What was that?
Are you alright?
Kid.
You came to rescue us!
Get over yourselves, I
don't give a crap about you!
Step aside!
Big Bob is mine!
Go ahead.
Keep coming at me.
I'm enjoying this.
That's no good, boy.
Hey, you're getting weaker.
What a shame.
Burned out already.
You came a long way, but it
seems this is as far as you go.
You've reached your limit.
Still grinning, are you?
Come on!
I'll knock you down again and again!
Oh, my God.
That's it over in an
instant though I shouldn't
be surprised the outcome
was clear from the start.
You got your hands on a powerful
weapon but it made you cocky.
You didn't think for a moment that
your Haki wouldn't be enough.?
You wouldn't dare to think it.
Because humans can't
stand to give up hope.
They refuse to.
So they believe in lies.
It's been a long time since I got
worked up enough to get sloppy.
I should have chopped your head
off and shown it to your friends.
They have to know you've lost.
Otherwise, they'll keep holding on to
the foolish hope that you'll return.